I'm only 4,600 square feet, and I did
a million dollars in revenue in one month.
Houston is one of the top 10 cities
in the entire world with the most millionaires.
Today, we're going to be asking
Houston millionaires how they became wealthy.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
Somewhere between 2.5 to 5 million.
Yeah.
That's incredible, man.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
The concierge space.
What exactly are you doing?
So basically, private jet charter, yacht
charter, exotic cars, the whole nine yards.
What is the best piece of advice
that you would tell your younger self?
Your network is your network.
Keep the right people around you who
push you, and that's all that matters.
You're going to go far in life that way.
Where are you from originally?
Nigeria.
Came a long way from back there, right?
Are you living in Houston now?
Yeah.
What was the best financial decision
that you ever made throughout your lifetime?
Just learn to hold on to money.
The trick to being financially well
off is being able to hold money.
A lot of people can make a lot of money, but
the trick is being able to hold on to that money.
So the moment I figured out how to
keep a lot of money, I was good.
First interview of the day.
He goes crazy.
Guy makes $2 to $5 million, has an
exotic car business, and he's a private jet concierge.
Let's see what else the day has in store.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Great question.
I started off doing computer science.
I was going to college because my parents expected
me to, but my heart really wasn't into it.
I later found my passion was
in the study of life and biology.
So I ended up becoming a doctor.
I'm an emergency room doctor now.
But even then, I switched industries.
I still am a doctor,
but I wanted to learn business.
I wanted to do business in real estate.
So now I'm building some lake homes on
the north side of town, but I'm still learning.
I'm in the early first couple years of that process.
So you are a business owner?
I am now, yeah.
So I think you got to follow your passion, but it's
okay for passions to be redirected as you get a little older.
I once heard a wise man say you should only have
a job long enough to learn what you can from it.
At that point, it's time to move on.
What is the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
I usually don't say that, but I guess for
the purposes of education, there's years where I lost money.
But the years where I made good
money, let's say around $4 to $5 million,
offset some losses and then reinvest that into growth.
And if you were to go back
to when you first started that business,
what is the number one thing
that you would have told yourself?
Yeah, you know, the first one's always the hardest.
It took me years to make it profitable.
You know, there was times where
I worked like 96 hours straight.
I think the biggest piece of advice on your
first business is going to be lose the ego.
Everybody wants to have a business.
Everybody wants to make money.
But when things aren't going right,
everybody wants to blame somebody else.
It doesn't matter if it's anybody else's fault.
It's your business.
Take the blame for everything.
Even if it's so-and-so that messed
up on it, it doesn't matter.
You picked them.
You got to ask yourself, how
could I have picked them better?
How can I train them better?
How can I motivate them better?
So if you lose the ego, blame yourself for everything,
then you'll always find the
right corrections to make it work.
Where do you think people
should look to invest their money
to try and grow and scale
the income that they do have?
I think rule number one in business is
almost everybody will try to take advantage of you,
especially when you're new and trusting.
So before I say that, I
say don't give it to anybody.
Investments are very tricky.
One is you got to save.
We said when you become 20 is when you
want to spend money on that new car right away.
I didn't have my first nice
car until I was 30 years old.
If you spend all your money too fast,
you won't be able to have the money
to invest in something that might have an opportunity.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
I'm in the marine industry.
I'm a ship captain.
Offshore oil and gas.
What is the best piece of advice
that you would tell your younger self?
Follow your dreams.
You only have one life and life is finite.
You're born, you die.
Everybody dies.
Follow your dreams.
Do everything with passion,
whether it's your work or
your pursuits, your hobbies, whatever.
Enjoy.
We're one of the most popular restaurants in Houston, Texas,
and we're going to go in and see
if we can get an interview with the owner.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Hospitality, restaurant business.
I started wedding tables at age
16 and I worked my way up
and now I own my own restaurant.
So you own this restaurant right here?
Yes, sir.
What is the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
Well, this past year, December, I'm only 4,600 square feet
and I did a million
dollars in revenue in one month.
And that's like $2,300, $2,400 a square foot.
Nobody in the city does that.
And what about for the whole year?
The whole year, I ended
up doing right under $10 million.
Most people would be happy doing
$4 million out of this size.
I did $10 million.
My goal is next year is to grow.
And what I do is
I tell all my key employees,
I will write you a check.
It could be $5,000, it could be $10,000.
If I reach out to
you, I'll write you a check.
If I reach this number
at the end of the year.
You were to go back to
when you started that first business,
what is the number one
thing that you would tell yourself?
Get everything written out in paperwork.
When you open a business with a partner,
always make sure there's a decision maker,
someone on the board of
directors that can make a decision
if you and your partner
do not agree on certain things.
Communication is key.
That's the number one thing in any successful business.
You got to communicate with your partner or your vendors
or whatever makes you successful.
How can someone become wealthy today?
I've heard from many wealthy billionaires.
They don't invest in businesses, they invest in people.
I'm here seven days a week.
Seven lunches, seven dinners.
I never leave.
I rarely take a break.
I got two Porsches in my garage.
They have no miles on them
because I'm never home to drive.
But I love what I do.
I wouldn't trade it for anything in the world.
So I think showing up and being 100% yourself
and being true to your business, just being there.
I know every customer on this patio.
I know every customer inside.
And I touch every single table.
I make everyone feel special.
You had brought up earlier that you never say no.
Can you kind of explain that?
In the restaurant business,
the last thing a customer wants to hear,
especially when he pulls up in
a Ferrari, is the word no.
So when they come in,
if we're fully booked with reservations,
we say,
we're fully committed at this point.
I never use the word no
because no one wants to hear that.
So I said, I can make anything happen.
That's my motto.
They want a car from the Rolls-Royce dealer delivered here.
I will go get it, add 20% to the check,
and bring them a Rolls-Royce.
I do not say no.
Gotta be one of my favorite interviews I've ever done.
An incredible guy all around
and just very thankful for his time.
I mean, this man is literally
in the middle of a lunch rush
right here on a Sunday afternoon at his restaurant
and took the time to come
answer a few questions for us.
We're seeing, we were watching him.
He's touching every table
and talking to every customer in there.
Damn, what a,
what a great entrepreneur, entrepreneur spirit, man.
We just saw Cam Jackson,
who's a really big entrepreneur on social media,
walking his dog.
So we're going to go after him,
see if we can get this interview real quick.
And what industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Real estate.
Yeah, so I do real estate investing.
And so are you a business owner by any chance?
Yes, I actually have some restaurants in Louisiana
and a shipping container park,
basically is what it is in Louisiana.
So what's your best advice to someone
who's trying to start buying property today?
I would say get into the areas
that are starting to gentrify,
but you got to get there early.
Find those areas,
find people that are investing already,
see where they're investing
and then get around schools,
anywhere that they're doing new HEBs
or doing, you know, Amazon shopping centers,
get there when they're doing those
and start getting some real estate there.
You were to go back to
when you started that first business,
what is the number one thing
that you would have told yourself?
Get around more people
that are doing what you want to do
and find a mentor.
Continue to get better.
You're always going to continue to get better.
Don't worry about being perfect.
And advice I'll tell somebody today,
just start.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
Most money?
Yeah.
Two million dollars.
What is the best piece of advice
that you would tell your younger self?
I would say that they need to think
in how to grow their own business
and not to be an employee.
So did you become a business owner?
I was an employee for 23 years,
but now I have my own company.
And if somebody will teach me
in the university
that the best will be
to have your own business,
I will follow that.
So what exactly is your company right now?
We are in the propane business.
We export propane into Mexico.
If you were to go back
to when you started that first business,
what is the number one thing
that you would have told yourself?
I would say the most important in life
is relationships.
How to through relationships,
do business.
That's the best.
What is the most important
piece of advice
that you would tell your younger self?
I dropped out of college.
I wouldn't really give myself
a lot of advice.
What industry did you ultimately
pursue a career in?
I mean, I was advertising sales
and I sold Lexus at 23.
Mortgage loan officer at 25.
And then I opened a mortgage company
and now I own a company,
worldclass.com,
where I import or sell
to fine restaurants.
So as an entrepreneur,
if you were to go back
to when you started
that first business,
what is the number one thing
that you would have told yourself?
I probably would have raised capital
and I would have surrounded myself
with really good people from day one.
Things that I've never done.
I've never raised capital.
I've never surrounded myself
day one with a great team.
You have those two things,
you're going to go.
When you're starting
to make that money though,
you're looking to kind of invest,
put it in different places.
I mean, real estate is number one.
And then you should have a cushion,
six to 12 months of your spend.
And then from there,
as far as stocks, S&P 500.
I mean, if Warren Buffett's
going to bet a million dollars
against the top 10 hedge funds
and win 10 out of 10 times
over a decade,
why are you going to try to be better
than the best Goldman Sachs?
I mean, just buy the S&P 500.
That's it.
What's the number one mindset change
that is needed in order
to become a multimillionaire?
You just can't be a sheep.
Let's say you get off the freeway
and you have 15 people in one lane.
Yeah.
And you can turn left
and there's one or two here.
Everyone just keeps lining up
behind that 50.
You can't just do
what everyone else is doing.
And you have to constantly
change yourself all the time.
What industry did you
ultimately pursue a career in?
I do medical sales.
I do implant sales.
I only do foot and ankle.
I don't do anything exciting.
What's the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
About 400, 500,000.
What has been your secret
to sales throughout your career?
You really have to push yourself
and you never say no.
You tell those doctors,
you tell whoever you're selling.
You want my product
because it's the best.
Keep showing them
your customer service.
You keep showing them yourself
because in sales,
it is you that they're buying.
It's your customer service.
It's your commitment to them
and making sure that they have
everything that they want
and you never give up on them.
Are you an investor?
I invest all my money.
What's your best investment advice
to the younger generation?
I think the key is that
you never stop investing in yourself.
You never stop investing in real estate.
If you were to go back
to when you were in either
high school or college
and you're having a conversation
with your 20-year-old self,
what is the most important
piece of advice
that you would tell your younger self?
Do exactly what I did.
Go to college
and get a degree in engineering.
Are you a business owner
by any chance?
No, no.
Just an electrical engineer
doing project management.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
And do you think a college degree
is necessary to be successful
in today's society?
No.
Why not?
Depends on your skill set.
So you might be
a brilliant entrepreneur
and be able to be an Elon Musk
or whoever
without having a college degree.
I don't think you have one.
And what industry
did you guys ultimately
pursue a career in?
Both of us are in real estate.
I built a home.
Commercial real estate.
What's your best advice
to anybody starting out in sales
in today's world?
You always sell yourself first.
If they like you,
they'll buy from you.
And ask a bunch of questions.
You know,
people will sell themselves
on you
if you ask enough questions.
What is the number one skill
that is needed
to be successful
in the business world?
What you just talked about.
If you can sell yourself,
I don't care what industry
you're in,
you can be an accountant,
you can be an engineer.
If you cannot sell yourself,
you're not going to be
successful anywhere.
That wraps up
our weekend in Houston.
Be sure to leave a like
and subscribe for tons
of amazing content coming soon.
And click this video right here
to watch us go around
wealthy neighborhoods
asking millionaires
how they got rich.